Gustavo Toledo

São Paulo 🏦

+55 (11) 9 8688-2668 📞

gusttaa00@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/gustaf-toledo in

cutt.ly/QIF9WfF

Young enthusiast who has grown up in the IoT era. Proficiency in Fullstack Development using JavaScript, TypeScript, Node, Angular, Nest and Knex. Database creation, modeling and analysis with SQL. Always researching paths to develop profit using modern and future Technologies.

Skills

- JavaScript (ES6+), TypeScript
- Node, Nest.js, Knex, Express
- Angular, React, etc.

- SQL (PGSQL, MSSQL, MySQL, SQLite...)
- Git, Gitlab, Bitbucket, Github...
- Agile and Design Thinking (Scrum)

Experience

SEPTEMBER 2020 - FEBRUARY 2021

Programmer Analyst Intern / Grupo Memorial

Maintenance and assistance of the ERP using Java/JSF; Using Angular, Nest.js and Knex to migrate the ERP; Trello integration for ticket opening using Automate.io; Developed the listing part of our intern framework, using Angular and Nest.js; Developed a full SDK for lugu (Financial Module) integration and a lot more.

AUGUST 2020 - OCTOBER 2020

Volunteer Web Developer / Centro Paula Souza

Leader and responsible for developing and deploying Fatec Guarulhos Web Site; Using React and Bootstrap for a SPA; Applied concepts of mobile first and clean-code; Deployment using Netlify.

Formation

FEBRUARY 2020 - DECEMBER 2022

Análise e Desenvolvimento de Sistemas / Fatec

Elected as Class Representant and has one of the highest grades between all Fatec's with a 9.15 PR.

Certifications

English Proficiency is Fluent; German Proficiency is Basic; Bokmål, Nynorsk Proficiency is Basic Technical Certificate Degree in Montagem e Recuperação de Computadores by Instituto Dom Bosco

Certificate Degree in Agile Meets Design Thinking by Coursera - University of <u>Virginia</u>
Certificate Degree in Introduction to IoT by Cisco Networking Academy